

Profile

I have a serious passion for UI effects, animations, and the creation of intuitive dynamic user experience. I can build fast, responsive, intuitive, and dynamic websites with the use of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python languages using Django and Flask frameworks. I am currently studying for a Diploma in Software Development through code Institute in a course that is aligned and accredited by Edinburgh Napier University.

Employment History

Customer Service Consultant at SUVEREN, Copenhagen-Denmark January 2019 — Present

I do help our customers with complaints and questions, give customers information about our products and services, take orders, and process returns.

Telephone Operator at First Choice Group Ltd, Nicosia-Cyprus

January 2016 — December 2018

Assist customers with special billing requests, such as charges to a third party and credits or refunds for incorrectly dialed numbers or bad connections. Handle emergency calls and assist children or people with physical disabilities to make telephone calls.

Education

Diploma in Software Development (pending), Code Institute, Dublin-Ireland

January 2020 — Present

Higher National Diploma in Marketing, Pan African Institute of Technology, Buea-Cameroon

 $September\,2010-December\,2013$

Courses

CS50: Introduction to Computer Science, HarvardX

January 2019 — April 2019

Details

+4531884865

takaforyannick30@gmail.com

Links

GitHub LinkedIn

Skills

HTML/HTML5

CSS/CSS3

JavaScript/JQuery

Python

SQL/NOSQL

Django/Flask

Languages

English

French